Christopher John Myers

22 Markington Place, Middleton, Leeds LS10 4TD Mobile: 07896 800811 Telephone: 0113 2707893 Email: chrisjohnmyers@gmail.com

Personal Statement

Well-motivated and resourceful professional. I work well autonomously and enjoy working within a team. Over 20 years' experience in both break-fix & preventative maintenance with hardware & software. Used to working on the front line and under pressure.

Key Skills - I am able to:

- Maintain good customer relations. Well practiced in face-to-face & telephone support or remote assistance.
- Provide Microsoft Office support, from Office 97 through to Office 2019. Also Outlook & Office 365.
- Manage Active Directory, from password changes to maintaining OU's, groups & objects.
- Install, maintain, repair & decommission Servers, PC's, switches, monitors, scanners, laser and inkjet printers.
- Prioritise tasks effectively with call queue management.
- Network infrastructure management & diagnostics.
- Maintain servers from Windows Server 2000 through to 2019.
- Collaborate with team members & create support documentation to allow others to complete tasks quickly.
- Manage mass rollout of software to clients via Group Policy & scripting.
- Experienced in managing WIFI access.
- Also competent in managing the following: Linux, CCTV, access control systems & telephony systems.
- Full UK driving license
- Basic First Aider

Employment History

William Henry Smith School - October 2017 to present

Boothroyd Lane, Brighouse, West Yorkshire, HD6 3JW

Technical support for IT systems including servers & network. Assisting users both face-to-face & over the telephone with technical issues for hardware & software.

Leeds South & East Foodbank - April 2017 to October 2017

7 Lenton Drive, Parkside Industrial Estate, LS11 5JW

Unpaid volunteer, filling any & all roles as needed. This included IT systems support, administration, warehouse assistant, food deliveries/collections and interviewing clients at the food centres.

Lightcliffe Academy - June 2009 to 31st January 2017

Stoney Lane, Lightcliffe, Halifax, HX3 8TL

Senior technical support for IT systems including servers & network. Mainly Windows with some Linux. Supervisory role for small team including job prioritising & monitoring.

Hammondsdirect, Bradford - July 2004 to March 2009

IT Support Analyst providing 1^{st} & 2^{nd} line support. Promoted to IT Support Specialist in 2007 providing 2^{nd} & 3^{rd} line support.

IBM UK LTD, Leeds/Bradford - July 1996 to July 2004

Computer hardware support engineer.

Bass Leisure Machines Services, Leeds - 1986 to July 1996

Field Service engineer for public house gaming & entertainment industry.

Ansell & Barbers, Armley, Leeds - 1984 to 1986

Video game repair & construction.

Microsoft official courses

- MS2272 Implementing and Supporting Microsoft Windows XP Professional
- MS2273 Managing and Maintaining a Microsoft Windows Server 2003
- MS2276 Implementing a Microsoft Windows Server 2003 Network Infrastructure: Network Hosts
- MS2277 Implementing a Microsoft Windows Server 2003 Network Infrastructure: Network Services
- MS50331 Supporting Windows 7 Desktops in the Enterprise
- M2400 Implementing & Managing Microsoft Exchange Server 2003

Qualifications

Microsoft Exam 070-270 - Installing, Configuring & Administering Microsoft Windows XP Professional Microsoft Exam 070-290 - Managing & maintaining Windows Server 2003 Environment IBM Netfinity & PC Server Systems Course: YPC35

IBM Netfinity Hardware Service Course: RN109

Compaq Desktops/Workstation & Notebooks (Compaq's own course)

Toshiba Computer Service Engineering CSE-G/I

Kitson College of Technology Electronics Servicing (City & Guilds) Parts I, II & III

G.C.E. 'O' Levels & C.S.E. - Seven, including Arithmetic, English

Interests

Music – I am currently taking lessons to learn to play the guitar.

Archery – I am a keen archer & I am member of NFAS.

Woodworking – Woodturning various objects, bow making (for archery) & making simple furniture.

Digital & video photography

Live theatre & cinema

Referees

Lisa King - Head of Support Services William Henry Smith School Boothroyd Lane Brighouse West Yorkshire HD6 3JW

01484 710123

lisa.king@whsschool.org.uk

Alan Godfrey - Line Manager for current role & also Lightcliffe Academy 21 Fairless Avenue Lightcliffe Halifax HX38XH

07784 985560 alangodfrey@me.com